const quizdata = [
    {
        question: "Javascript is an____language?",
        options: [
            "Object-Oriented",
            "Object-Based",
            "Procedural",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: 1
    }, {
        question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript",
        options: [
            "var",
            "let",
            "Both A and B",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: 3
    }, {
        question: "Which of the following is used to access HTML element Javascript?",
        options: [
            "getElementbyId()",
            "getElementByClassName()",
            "Both A and B",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: 1
    }, {
        question: "Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?",
        options: [
            "Throws an error",
            "Ignore the statements",
            "Gives a warning",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
        options: [
            "document.write()",
            "console.log()",
            "window.alert()",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        options: [
            "const",
            "var",
            "let",
            "constant"
        ],
        answer: 1
    }, {
        question: "When an operator's value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unarry operator is:",
        options: [
            "Boolean",
            "Undefined",
            "Object",
            "Integer"
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
        options: [
            "stringify()",
            "parse()",
            "convert()",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following are in Javascript?",
        options: [
            "Variables",
            "Functions",
            "Objects",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a javascript framework?",
        options: [
            "Node",
            "vue",
            "React",
            "Cassandra"
        ],
        answer: 4
    }, {
        question: "What Keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in javascript",
        options: [
            "async",
            "await",
            "setTimeout",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How do we write a comment in Javascript?",
        options: [
            "/**/",
            "//",
            "#",
            "$$"
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following are not server-side Javascript object?",
        options: [
            "Date",
            "FileUpload",
            "Function",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following attribute can hold the JavaScript version?",
        options: [
            "Language",
            "Script",
            "Version",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Inside which HTML element do we put the javascript?",
        options: [
            "<js>",
            "<scripting>",
            "<script>",
            "<javascript>"
        ],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which type of image maps can be used with JavaScript?",
        options: [
            "Server-Side image maps",
            "Client-side image maps",
            "Both A and B",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the client-side JavaScript object?",
        options: [
            "Database",
            "Cursor",
            "Client",
            "FileUpload"
        ],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the server-side JavaScript object?",
        options: [
            "FileUpload",
            "Function",
            "File",
            "Date"
        ],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not considered a Javascript operator?",
        options: [
            "new",
            "this",
            "delete",
            "typeof"
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Javascript is interpreted by______",
        options: [
            "Client",
            "Server",
            "Object",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Using____statement is how you test for a specific condition.",
        options: [
            "Select",
            "if",
            "Switch",
            "For"
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Is it possible to nest functions in JavaScript?",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Both A and B",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the client-side Javascript object:",
        options: [
            "Database",
            "Cursor",
            "Client",
            "FileUpload"
        ],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Js stands for :",
        options: [
            "java",
            "javascript",
            "jvm",
            "jsx"
        ],
        answer: 2
    }
];

export default quizdata

